myworkdaycdn.com 2014-10-24

# Workday Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Statement

Data Privacy is important to Workday, Inc. (“Workday”). This privacy statement informs visitors of what data Workday gathers on its Web sites, how will use it and with whom we share it. If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, contact [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com) or see the “Contact Us” section later in this policy.

This privacy policy describes the information we collect about you as a visitor to our Web sites [www.workday.com](http://www.workday.com/) and [www.peoplearethenewbottomline.com](http://www.peoplearethenewbottomline.com/). The following tells you how we use this information and describes your choices regarding certain types of processing.

##### Information Collected

Workday collects and retains contact information for you as a visitor only if you voluntarily supply us with this information. You may choose to provide us with this information, including your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number or other information, to access protected information on our Web sites or so we can follow up with you after your visit. If you have voluntarily provided this information, you consented to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information as described in this privacy statement. In addition, Workday may combine other publicly available information related to the organization from which you work for with the information that you provide to us. 

Workday does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information collected through its Web sites with third parties for their sole promotional purposes or as otherwise outlined in this policy.

Workday may share information with third parties who resell the Workday service and/or provide value added services such as payroll outsourcing, tax filing, and other administrative services for our Mid-Market Channel offering. Workday’s Mid-Market Channel offering is designed to meet the needs of customers that have fewer than 1,500 employees. When you sign up for webinars, download white papers, or generally inquire about Workday’s offering and/or services, we will share contact information and product interest as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

Workday may disclose information in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights or property; (c) enforce the Web site Terms and Conditions of Use; or (d) act to protect the interests of our users or others.

If Workday goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information collected through our Web site(s) may be among the assets transferred. A prominent notice will appear on our Web site(s) for 30 days after any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

##### Use of Web Site(s)

Workday, or Workday-authorized service providers, may observe your activities, preferences, and transactional data relating to your use of our Web site(s) and our services. While we may collect or log this information, we do not identify you or match this information with your other personal information (such as your IP address) unless you have chosen to identify yourself by completing a contact form on the Web site. We may use this collected or logged information to diagnose web site technical problems. Workday or our authorized service provider may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our Web site(s). If you have submitted contact information via forms on a site, Workday may use information from cookies and web beacons to provide you with information about the Company and the Service.

##### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that our Web sites ask to place on your computer's hard drive. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We do not use cookies to read any other information on your computer's hard drive. We use cookie technology to authenticate your access to various areas of our Web sites, and tailor its content to your preferences. Cookies help us analyze web traffic in general and to track when site visitors complete surveys. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed.

We also use web beacons, or transparent GIF files, provided by our service provider to report activity on our site. The beacons help us manage our online advertising and measure its effectiveness. These files enable our service provider to recognize a cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements are most effective. Either Workday or our services providers place the cookie. The information that we collect by means of these technologies is anonymous. It is not personally identifiable unless you have chosen to identify yourself through a form on the Web site.

##### Retargeted Advertising

Retargeted advertising uses information collected on an individual's web browsing behavior such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is used to display more relevant information to you on the Workday website. This information is also used to display Workday employment opportunities to you if you have visited our careers page. The information collected is only linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising either comes from Workday or through third party website publishers. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent cookies or to notify you each time a cookie is set. If you would like to opt out of retargeted advertising from Workday, please [click here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

##### Customer Data

As part of Workday's services, customers may load data into Workday servers. Workday will not share or distribute any such customer data except as provided in the contractual agreement between Workday and customer, or as may be required by law. [Please refer to the Workday Service Privacy Policy for more details.](http://www.workday.com/company/service_privacy.php "Workday Service Privacy Policy")

##### Data Processing

Any personal data collected about EU visitors via our Web sites is processed in the United States by Workday or by a party acting on its behalf. When you provide personal data to Workday, you consent to the processing of your data in the United States. Our Web sites are hosted in the United States.

##### Third-Party Web Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that Workday does not own or control. Please be aware that Workday is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Web sites. We suggest that you read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by Workday Web sites.  
We post customer testimonials on our Web sites which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com)

##### Online Forums

On our Web sites, you may post comments, for example on a blog or bulletin board. These comments and discussions are moderated, and may be accessed or deleted for technical or other reasons. We will not use the information you post on an online forum beyond the purpose for which you posted it. You should only post personal information to online forums with the awareness that the information will be made available to others inside and outside of Workday. Any comments posted by individuals on an online forum, such as a blog, are his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of Workday. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

##### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web sites include Social Media Features, such as YouTube videos, the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our sites. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

##### Security

Workday employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. However, the security of information transmitted through the Internet can never be guaranteed. Workday is not responsible for any interception or interruption of any communications through the Internet or for changes to or losses of data. Users of our sites are responsible for maintaining the security of any password, user ID, or other form of authentication involved in obtaining access to password protected or secure areas of any Workday sites. In order to protect you and your data, Workday may suspend your use of a site, without notice, pending an investigation, if any breach of security is suspected. Access to and use of password protected and/or secure area of any Workday site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized access to such areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution.

##### Opt-Out

If at any time after registering for information, you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com). Use the same email address if you do not wish to receive our newsletters, including the Workday newsletter. 

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, or if you need to update, change or remove information, you can do so by contacting [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com) or by regular mail addressed to:

Workday, Inc.   
Attn: Privacy   
6230 Stoneridge Mall Road   
Pleasanton, CA 94588   
United States

Workday will respond to your correction or update request within at most 30 days from the date of your request.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us via the information above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Changes to this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate. Posting those changes will inform you of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by email.

##### TRUSTe Privacy Program Statement

Workday has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html). These requirements include transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@workday.com](mailto:privacy@workday.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can [contact TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). This TRUSTe certification covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through our applications.

##### Safe Harbor Program Statement

Workday complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland respectively. Information regarding the both the E.U. and Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: [export.gov/safeharbor](http://export.gov/safeharbor).

##### APEC Program Statement

Workday’s privacy practices described in this Statement comply with the [APEC Cross Border Privacy Rules System](http://www.apec.org/Groups/Committee-on-Trade-and-Investment/~/media/Files/Groups/ECSG/CBPR/CBPR-PoliciesRulesGuidelines.ashx). 

_Last Updated on June 09, 2014_
